

## CONTACT

- +37493142243
- +37495142240
- mesropyanarman21@gmail.com
- Armenia, Yerevan

## SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS, SASS, LESS
- JAVASCRIPT
- TYPESCRIPT
- REACT.JS
- REDUX
- GIT

# LANGUAGES

- ARMENIAN [NATIVE]
- RUSSIAN [ADVANCED]
- ENGLISH [MEDIUM]

# ARMAN MESROPYAN

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

### **PROFILE**

I appreciate high-quality, competent work with teammates and an increased sense of

responsibility in every job. Any new project motivates me gain new knowledge and experience

In work I rate highly `

- Honesty
- Teamwork
- Punctuality
- A responsibility
- Time management
- Interpersonal communication

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### O FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **GROUP 404**

Mar.2022 - Now

What am I doing here?

- I work on react and typescript in different projects, mostly admin and not only.
- Implementing a responsive approach focused on mobile devices.
- Collaboration with product team members to implement a new feature
- Coordinating with the web development team to design user interfaces for client websites using JavaScript, TypeScript, React.JS. Developing and coding web applications for customer accounts, including debugging problems, diagnosing root causes, and identifying solutions.

# FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT TUTOR

#### **GROUP 404**

Nov.2022 - Now

What am I doing here?

- I teach FrontEnd development
- HTML
- CSS
- SCSS/SASS
- Javascript

# EDUCATION

SMART CODE

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT

2021

YERVAN STATE COLLEGE OF INFORMATICS

SECONDARY SPECIALIZED EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

# EVENTS

BUISSUP GLOBAL FORUM

2022

WE PARTICIPATED IN THE BISSUP GLOBAL FORUM PROJECT WITH A GREAT IDEA AND WON 1ST PLACE.

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Oct.2021 - Mar.2022

#### **SHARP BRAINS**

What did I do there?

- user interface development
- creating an adaptive application
- creating a functional application
- creating an HTML page of the site based on design layouts
- binding to the user interface of scripts that provide visualization
- and animation of the site pages;
- Development of Single Page Applications: React.js